I'm not afraid to go to a regular prison.
Some of the girls are, and I feel for them
just as I feel for myself and my family.
To see the girls crying at night, how sore
they are.
They do 90 sets of push-ups, sit-ups for a
woman.
It's crazy.
crime, attempted assault in the second,
and I violated probation.
I'm 18 years old.
For fighting, and this is a good
discipline program for people that have
problems dealing with stress, things like
that.
I came in a woman.
I want to leave a woman.
I have children at home to go home to.
I don't want my mind mentally.
I don't want to be strong.
I don't want to be fit with him.
This inmate is released and goes out there
and commits some horrendous crime because
I put them on the
street.
Yeah, I take that very seriously.
So I spend a lot of time with these,
paying attention to these inmates.
And if I'm not comfortable with it, she's
not being released.